https://www.deardiary.net/about/privacy-policy

Skip to content
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DearDiary.Net collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.deardiary.net website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by DearDiary.Net.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
DearDiary.Net may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
– To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.– To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.– To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
DearDiary.Net has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:By e-mail to: contact@DearDiary.Net
You can also click the Contact Us button at the top of the home page.
This document was last updated on February 28, 2020
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Comment
April 2020 (1)
March 2020 (2)
February 2020 (5)
December 2019 (1)
November 2019 (1)
October 2019 (4)
February 2015 (2)
February 2014 (1)
December 2013 (1)
August 2013 (1)
July 2013 (1)
February 2013 (3)
December 2012 (1)
July 2012 (12)
June 2012 (9)
May 2012 (2)
April 2012 (3)
December 2011 (2)
November 2011 (3)
September 2011 (2)
August 2011 (2)
July 2011 (1)
May 2011 (1)
April 2011 (2)
January 2011 (3)
December 2010 (1)
October 2010 (4)
September 2010 (7)
July 2010 (2)
June 2010 (13)
May 2010 (1)
October 2009 (3)
September 2009 (1)
May 2009 (2)
April 2009 (2)
February 2009 (1)
January 2009 (2)
September 2008 (2)
August 2008 (1)
July 2008 (1)
June 2008 (6)
January 2008 (2)
November 2007 (1)
October 2007 (1)
September 2007 (1)
May 2007 (2)
November 2006 (3)
September 2006 (7)
August 2006 (12)
April 2006 (3)
February 2006 (2)
January 2006 (4)
December 2005 (10)
November 2005 (6)
October 2005 (2)
September 2005 (1)
August 2005 (1)
July 2005 (3)
May 2005 (1)
April 2005 (1)
March 2005 (2)
February 2005 (4)
January 2005 (9)
December 2004 (7)
November 2004 (8)
October 2004 (19)
September 2004 (10)
August 2004 (5)
July 2004 (2)
June 2004 (1)
May 2004 (16)
April 2004 (16)
March 2004 (3)
February 2004 (9)
January 2004 (27)
December 2003 (26)
November 2003 (1)
October 2003 (5)
September 2003 (1)
May 2003 (1)
March 2003 (1)
February 2003 (1)
January 2003 (4)
December 2002 (4)
October 2002 (1)
August 2002 (2)
July 2002 (2)
June 2002 (6)
May 2002 (9)
April 2002 (7)
March 2002 (8)
February 2002 (5)
January 2002 (8)
December 2001 (11)
November 2001 (26)
October 2001 (17)
September 2001 (13)
August 2001 (16)
July 2001 (30)
June 2001 (10)
May 2001 (44)
April 2001 (21)
March 2001 (20)
February 2001 (13)
January 2001 (12)
December 2000 (2)
November 2000 (4)
October 2000 (14)
September 2000 (2)
August 2000 (5)
July 2000 (2)
November 1999 (1)
October 1999 (6)
September 1999 (13)
DearDiary.Net is Copyright © 1999-2020 Most Useful
DearDiary.Net - Free Online Diary / Journal since 1999
Copyright Notice: All diary entries are copyright of their respective authors.
Do not use without their prior written consent
Complaints or DMCA requests please Contact Us
